#### SOURABH DUBEY

Sch. N. 54, Indore, M.P. India PIN - 452001 Sourabh.sr.dubey@gmail.com

Mobile: +91-9425033770

#### **PROFILE**

A versatile Equity Analyst with more than five years of experience in the equity research. With quality driven work ethics and having an exceptional track record I am seeking analyst position in the industry to apply accrued experience in contributing towards the achievement of the organizational objectives.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

- 1. Working with Alpha Investment Adviser, Indore, India as a Senior Research Analyst (Research Manager). Since Nov. 2017 to till date.
- 2. Working with CapVision Research, Indore, India as a Senior Research Analyst. Since April 2017 to Oct. 2017.
- 3. Working with Trade India Research, Indore, India as a Senior Research Analyst. Since Feb. 2014 to March 2017.

# **Roles and responsibilities**

Provide investment tips based on Technical Analysis (Equity Market).

Viz. intraday and positional basis.

Client interactions and provide investment advice.

Preparing day wise report of Equity Analysis report.

## **Key Experience**

Working on Ticker Plant for Technical Analysis.

Understanding dynamics of Equity market in order to ensure right investment decision for clients.

Assisting clients for helping them to take prudent entry and exit decision.

Assisting seniors in terms of client interaction and preparing day to day investment reports.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certificate of Six-Sigma Quality white belt program.

Case base workshop to analysis the problems.

Six month training certificate of Tally 9, A Financial Accounting Program.

## FINANCIAL TRAINING

Eight weeks of fundamental training in stock market through Swastika Investmart Ltd. Indore, India. Two months training of Technical Analyst from Swastika Investmart Ltd. Indore.

## **UNDERTAKING AREAS**

Stock market

**Derivatives** 

Financial research

Commodities

## **EDUCATION**

MBA in Finance from DAVV, Indore, India, completed in 2012. B. Com. in Taxation from DAVV, Indore, India, completed in 2008.

## **COMUTER SKILLS**

Proficiency in basic office tools like Microsoft Word, Excel and Presentation

Financial Accounting Program Tally 9

## **LANGUAGES**

English & Hindi

## PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: October 15, 1988.

Date:

Place: Indore SOURABH DUBEY